All right, everybody. Welcome to Q4 as
we kick off after a pretty good Q3. I'm
joined as ever by Guy from Coin Bureau
and 20 other channels. Guy, how you
doing?
>> I'm all right, thanks Rob.
>> And of course, Ben, Bitcoin dominance,
my man. How you doing?
>> Pretty good. How about you?
>> Ah, pretty good. I wanted to uh dive
into this and get going. Time is
valuable, especially with what we have
for today. Now, this is the first day of
Q4, and it's uh quite an interesting
time frame, especially as we go from uh
the all-time high, which was just one
year ago in five days, as uh October 6,
2026 is coming up to us quite quickly.
And we had a massive massive Q3. We can
see right here on this website. I don't
know if you guys are familiar with this.
It's into the cryptoverse. There's a
link in the description where you can
check it out. There's a lot of things
that are are free, but there's some
really good stuff behind the the payw
wall, which is worth it. But we can see
that uh July, August, September, let me
zoom in on this, was a pretty good
quarter, which uh some saw coming, some
did not. It doesn't really matter. I
mean, dollar cost average works out
okay. 7% 25% in September and we haven't
had a quarter like that since the last
one was 2017 where we had this massive
8% 67%
positive month and then a down month. So
the question I have going across all
different things is it's October 1st
today. So only got five more days till I
reach the previous cycle. So far Q3 has
been great. So what broke?
Was it the cycle itself? Was there
something going on in the macro hiding
behind everything or was it like an
unnatural exuberance for AI AI plays and
the picks and shovels that has to deal
with AI? And uh Ben kick that off and
then we'll ask guy with an additional
question.
>> I mean I don't think any I don't think
you could argue that anything broke. I
mean the we Bitcoin normally has 40%
rallies in Q3. Um this was a 50% rally,
right? So it it did go up a little bit
more than it normally does. Uh, and it
did go higher than I thought it would.
Um, looking back, you know, if the low
if the July low is the low, which as
long as we're above 83K, you know, I
mean, certainly the the the burden of
proof has shifted to the bears, not the
bulls. Um, I I think we would look back
at this in 20 years and still say that
look, in the midterm year, Bitcoin went
down and it went below the 200E moving
average, right? Which is what it did in
the cycle before and the cycle before
that. and like this is just what always
happens. But when you're living through
it, it feels right like it it obviously
feels uh very different. But I mean when
we've talked about the four-year cycle
in the past and and in the context of
the S&P 500, there are times like most
of the time the S&P would bottom in Q4
and then occasionally it would bottom
earlier in the year, right? So it's not
it's not an exact science. And then as
far as it being a year out from the
prior all-time high, um I you know I I I
sort of heard someone say this, but it's
it's not really over until we're through
the fourth quarter as well, right? Like
it's hard to hard to jump to conclusions
about things um before we even get
through Q4 because, you know, in some
ways if if we do break if we do break
back down, that doesn't mean we need to
go back to a new low, right? I'm not
saying that that's a necessity, but
there there could still be some type of
event that spooks people. Um, and we'll
see if that happens. I mean, I I
certainly have no idea. Uh, with Bitcoin
holding 83K, it's shattered my
expectations. So, I'm trying to be a
little bit more I'm trying to be less
deterministic about about about this
stuff. Uh but yeah, I mean I think um
if if you look at the length of the the
last two cycles, it would actually put
this one not towards early October, but
towards like late October. Um because I
think a couple of them were what 54
weeks instead of
>> 500 days, but yeah, roughly.
>> I mean, so we we'll see what happens. I
think the right now you have the long
end of the old curve going up and
normally what happens is at least what's
happened this year with the long end is
the long end goes up and then Bitcoin
either stays flat or goes up slightly
and then when the long end goes down
then Bitcoin has has dropped and you
know with Bitcoin taking out the May
high right like it it kind of has has
certainly caught a lot of things into
question but look it's surprising you
know if you told me that the dollar,
like if that the dollar was going to be
going up, which is what I thought, and
you told me energy prices were going to
be going up and that the 30-year yield
was, you know, at at 5.7 or 5.6% and the
10-year was breaking 5.3 and all this
stuff. I would not have assumed that
Bitcoin would be trading at 83K. Uh, but
I mean, it just goes to show that
markets, as you know, they don't have to
conform to our expectations and um, you
know, other things can happen. Yeah,
that is the truth. I mean, we had a lot
of expectations, but you know, I thought
it was going to go down, too, but uh you
know, here we are. And you know, it's a
good thing that we just stay in the
game. And the people that are watching
this video, you're the ones that were
buying in the bear. So, congratulations
because it ain't easy throwing sand in
the ocean. Guy, same type of question,
but a little bit of an add-on here. So,
what Ben was talking about made a lot of
sense. So, the four-year cycles, is that
still the right lens to take a look at
things? and do the ETFs really change
how things are have gone especially as
we get out and as a reminder I mean we
had a pretty massive setup for this for
this last cycle we had you know the
foundation was there ETFs in 2024 Black
Rockck Fidelity you had government
support CFTC and SEC comes in because
they can't because Congress can't pass
clarity and uh this guy did some things
and you had the DATs and digital asset
treasuries so across that board look
pretty good so did the ETFs change a
thing or do you think it's not a big
deal and we'll just keep going along?
I think the ETF's definitely changed how
capital finds its way into crypto and
what it then does after that because in
previous years, in previous cycles, it's
been a case of capital gets its way
finds its way on chain via exchanges
into Bitcoin. And then as Bitcoin
holders, you know, as their as their
investment goes up, they became more
tempted to go and explore kind of higher
risk stuff that would take them out
along the risk curve and into altcoins.
And you know, then we get this kind of
across the board meltup. And what ETFs
did is is completely shut that route
off. So capital still finds its way into
Bitcoin, but it's through this regulated
rapper um that it doesn't generally tend
to move out of. If it moves out, uh it,
you know, maybe it would go to a spot
ETH ETF, but it will probably go, you
know, back out into into someone's
brokerage account and be reallocated
elsewhere, you know, most likely to to
stocks or commodities or, you know,
other assets that aren't crypto. So in
that case, yeah, I the ETFs have changed
because capital just doesn't enter
crypto and and then, you know, disperse
through crypto like it once did. And
that's not to say that that doesn't
happen. It's not to say that new money
doesn't find its way in, but really, you
know, the old dynamic of how a crypto
bull market worked has has has changed,
has been broken, if you like, by by the
ETF. So yeah, I think that's been a big
change and it's taken a bit of time to
get used to and I'm sure there are
plenty of people who disagree with me on
that, but that is the way that's the way
I see it and and you know I haven't I've
yet to be convinced otherwise. So yeah,
that's changed an awful lot. And then as
you know as to what's kind of happened
recently I Ben made a very interesting
point about you know how there's always
something you know people are easily
spooked uh when you know in in crypto
times like this and yeah I mean what
better what better illustration of that
you as you point out we're five days off
the high from last year. We're also 10
days off uh the or nine days off I
should say the um the day when crypto
lost more you know many multiples uh of
of billions were evaporated in a single
day many multiples more than than went
down the tubes when FTX collapsed you
know we're only we're just over a week
away from from the anniversary of the
10th of October um which was an absolute
catastrophe in which you know in in many
ways I think we're sort of still
recovering from. So, you know, this
that's a good that's as good an
illustration of any of how quickly this
market can change and how quickly
sentiment can change.
>> No, it's a great answer. And then this
will this will go into the next the next
question which I'm going to direct right
towards you guy. Same thing. So, you
just talked about just all the things
that I mean we've got what you say nine
10 days away from that anniversary. So,
that's an interesting thing because in
Q3 we saw a massive runup even though we
had all these problems and Ben talked
about those as well. But we've got I
mean the Fed the Fed hiked. It looks
like they're going to hike again. Looks
like they're going to hike also in
December. So, we're going to have three
rate hikes potentially. I'm not saying
it is. I don't have a crystal ball. And
then, of course, we've also got uh
treasuries and we just had 10 year, 20
year, 30 year. We're at 5.2, six, 5.6 uh
across the board. So I mean we have a
lot of looks like and also inflation uh
is going up after all those things that
have been happening. We still have seen
quite a rip. So the question that I have
for for you and Ben I'll start with you
guy is what's the market seeing in the
crypto space that other people are like
no no no you don't understand this is
how it's going to be. Yeah, and it's as
Ben said, it is so surprising that under
these conditions, Bitcoin and and crypto
more more generally have gone up because
it's totally counterintuitive. So, I
mean, my best guess is that if if you
take those things you talked about, if
you take the Fed, you know, the Fed has
hiked interest rates and is probably
going to do so again before the end of
the year, that's an inflation story,
>> right?
>> The the 10-year yield is at 5 point
5.25. And I mean the 30-year yield is
even higher. You know, these are
multi-deade highs. That's also kind of
an inflation story, but that's also a
story about borrowing out of control and
essentially essentially uh fiat
currencies becoming worthless. Um you've
also got clarity dying in the Senate.
You know, I think what I think a crucial
a crucial thing is that Bitcoin isn't
really affected by the Clarity Act. The
Clarity Act is much more about stable
coins and and tokenization and and
things like that. You know, Bitcoin
itself is a much more neutral asset. If
I had to guess, my my best guess would
be uh you know, you could point to
Bitcoin's correlation with gold has
become the highest it's been in years. I
think this is a story about people
looking at looking at the dollar and
looking at fiat currencies more
generally because as you said the
dollar's up so other currencies are
doing even worse and people looking at
this and going I need not necessarily an
off-ramp but I need something that is
outside of this system because what do
you like everyone knows $40 trillion of
debt is just and and it's only going up
like everyone knows that doesn't get
paid off like that's just not going
away. So I I think Bitcoin particularly
is is is the only way that many people
see out of that that and gold and I
think that correlation as I said with
gold being so high is is probably not a
coincidence. I think there are serious
concerns around sovereign debt and the
dollar and also just around the
competence of governments and and the
people who are responsible for this. I
mean, you look at Scott Bessant's uh
attempted intervention in the bond
market, which kind of set this whole
rally off, you know, just just last
month or whenever it was, you know, that
didn't work. That did that did
absolutely nothing. And I think that was
an instructive moment as well because
people are like, okay, these guys want
to do something, but there's actually
nothing they can do. And I think that
was a powerful reminder of just how bad
this debt situation is.
>> Yeah. And it's well said and I think
it's it's it just really does come back
to just the basics the basics of basics.
We take a look at the debasement of the
of the currency and we can see that
there's so much debt out there. I mean
the M2 money supply of course just
they're going to keep printing. So why
wouldn't we get into assets especially
as we are careening into what I think is
at some point we have to have a
recession. I'm not saying it's in six
months or in a year or three years but I
mean these are the things and just for a
little context this is the national debt
today. In 1980, this was the national
debt. So, as we take a look at this and
we and we go back and forth, like, wow,
the government's really going to get us.
The government's not going to do
anything but get put us in a bigger
hole. So, it's up to us to make sure
that we are protected. So, Ben, the same
question for you, guy. Well answered.
But I'll add something else. Does this
make you more bullish or more nervous? I
mean, we just talked about some pretty
nervous things, the wall of worry,
considering we just had the best quarter
since 2017 and we are on a nice little
rally still. So taking all that, what do
you think
>> about the markets in general?
>> About Sorry. Yeah. About the markets
right now moving into Q4 and and you did
say, you know, in the beginning, you're
like, look, this has happened before.
The Q4 is going to if history repeats
itself, can it can be pretty awful.
>> Usually what happens is is commodities
bottom. So commodities go down while the
dollar and yields go up, which is kind
of what's happening. Gold and silver are
dropping. And then what what I would
look for is when normally commodities
bottom before yields top and normally
the dollar tops before yields top as
well I believe. So if we start seeing
strength in gold uh and normally gold
starts showing some strength kind of
like in the November like later October
November time frame if we start seeing
strength in metals then we're probably
near the top in yields. So then the
question becomes when yields top which
in 2022 and in 2026 or sorry 2018 and
2022 yields topped in like the late
October to early November time frame. So
if yields top in late October, early
November,
then when they come down, why are they
coming down? And and and the reason why
they come down should then dictate
what's actually happening in the risk
assets. Because if you look at if you
look at small caps like the Russell or
the equal weight S&P, that stuff's going
down right now. Like the Russell's down
almost 10%. And the reason is because
the Russell is more rate sensitive than
than, you know, the Mag 7, right? The
Mag 7 is it's not as important for them
to worry about rates nearly as much when
they have just so many billions of
dollars in cash just sitting there. Uh,
you know, it's a lot easier for them to
make it through harder times, whereas a
lot of companies are are struggling a
lot more. So, what's interesting is that
in 2018, the Russell started dropping
about a month before the S&P did. Now,
the reason why it's hard is because I
would say like 70% of the time, maybe
even 80% of the time, when the Russell
drops, the S&P eventually also drops.
Like the large caps eventually get the
memo. But there are some times where
it's the Russell that kind of catches
back up to the S&P. and the Russell will
likely we we'll figure that out whenever
yields top. So, and so then we have to
figure out why are yields topping? If
they're topping, let's say yields top
because the war in the Middle East comes
to an end and all of a sudden the energy
trade is no longer a trade. And if
yields come down for that reason, then
that would probably be bullish, right?
That would actually be more bullish
because then you probably have the
Russell catching up to the S&P, right?
But if yields top because there's a
growth scare which can often happen
after the long end goes up all the you
know borrowing costs go up uh a lot of
things change and then there's there can
be a growth scare then what happens is
that the S&P then goes down to where the
Russell is and the Russell goes even
lower and and that's what we saw happen
in in 2018 and and in some of the other
you know periods that were were like
this and actually if you look at the
lows in the market this year uh for
Bitcoin and I believe for the S&P they
actually correspond to the long end of
the yield curve going down. So the long
end went down in March and you know sort
of the March April time frame that's
where or February March time frame
that's where we had that first low in
the S&P. We also saw the long end go
down in the summer that's where we had
that correction in the S&P. So, a lot of
times you don't even see the S&P show
any weakness until closer to the time
that that yields are topping. And that's
why in in 2014 and 2018, the weakness
didn't even really show up in the S&P
until October, especially in uh in 2018,
right? I mean, in 2018, the S&P was
basically at all-time highs even on
October 3rd. And it wasn't until after
yields topped where it showed that
weakness. So, I think a lot of it is
just going to depend on why do yields
top, right? Are they topping because of
a growth scare or are they topping
because
>> the war in the Middle East finally comes
to an end and then oil prices drop 20 to
$30 overnight and then that's a and that
if it's that that would be a reason to
be more so in the bull camp and I I
think that's going to be the the main
thing to think about is is what is the
narrative for why yields top and my
guess is they'll probably top within the
next four to six weeks.
>> Good answer Ben as usual. How much time
have you thought about that over and
over in your head as to how these things
are going to play out?
>> Well, I just published a report
yesterday about it. So, that's why I was
Yeah.
>> Yeah, that makes a lot of sense. All
right. So, so great answer, gentlemen.
Thank you. Moving along and then we'll
get to the Q&A pretty quickly. Is we're
going to switch gears a little bit just
to altcoins because it seems like, you
know, this last quarter was pretty good
for Bitcoin, but it was great for some
altcoins. Not so much all of them, but
that's just pretty much how it is. So,
I'm going to direct this to Guy since he
has a couple of different channels
devoted to this. Altcoins, they're
ripping and it comes back. It's on the
back of a bunch of big announcements,
right?
Zcash,
which I still don't understand why this
rip so much because it had an
announcement of Grayscale's ETF, put an
ETF up. So, it's up 65% in three months,
but over like a year, 18 months, it's up
like over 800. It's it's exa ridiculous.
Salana ETFs have had inflow for 12
straight weeks. Near is pivoting from an
L1 to a cross trading trading and
payments for AI agents which is also a
big thing. Quant just hu had had a huge
moment. They were selected for a
interoperability rank in a in a bankled
uh tokenized money network clearing
house and for US payments. So the whole
thing is this is these altcoins have
gone up and to me personally I always
thought it was it was it's always three
parts speculation one part utility. just
give me a tiny bit of utility and a
boatload of speculation and we can have
this market actually move, but does it
really mean that's going to be
sustainable? So, what's your take on
this after everybody who in the coin
bureau had been taking a look at it?
>> Yeah, the quant one is interesting. I I
I I I said on Twitter that, you know,
the announcement of a a coin a crypto
coin pumping on the announcement of a
partnership with a Trafi uh entity is so
old school, you know, it's so sort of
2017 2021, you know, the sort of stuff.
Oh, wow. You know, this is it. Crypto's
going mainstream. I must I I'll be
honest with you. I don't know quite how
consequential this clearing house um
announcement is like you know because
crypto is very good at doing these
things like you know announcements of
announcements or announcements of
partnerships and stuff and actually they
turn out to be like you know a bit of a
nothing burger but I'm going to reserve
judgment on the quant one because I
don't actually know but um I do think
it's really interesting to see that sort
of price action off this you know off
this sort of announcement because you
know that that hasn't that happened a
lot in the past, but it hasn't really
happened more recently. Um, yeah, you
know, you mentioned a lot, you mentioned
a lot of projects there. Zcash, yeah, is
benefiting from this whole uh privacy
narrative. It's um and as you say,
things like Grayscale's ETF as well. I
think there's also an element of like,
you know, quantum resistance and
is this a is this a possible alternative
to Bitcoin? Um then you've got I mean
Salana has okay Salana's been pretty
beaten down but uh Soul is is still a
pretty useful coin to hold if you're
going to go and uh trench it over on
over on Salana near again has a near
intense which I think I'm seeing some
news of near intense maybe getting
exploited but I'm not too sure of that
but um yeah again like a a project that
has uh that has demonstrated some real
utility. Now, I guess the questions that
arise from all this is like, is is all
of this price action, is it down to new
capital? Is new capital finding its way
into the crypto ecosystem? Um, and,
you know, does that mean that new people
are coming on board? I I'm not sure
that's necessarily the case. Sure, some
of it will be will be new capital, but I
do I do get the sense that this is kind
of capital rotating around.
Nevertheless, there's there's kind of
good news out there. Clarity failed, but
the SEC has kind of picked up picked up
the bat. It's um you know, it's working
uh working on regulations that I mean,
there's a fair bit of speculation now
that this could lead to a sort of ICO
boom 2.0 because of what they're going
to let it do. Um I I think you know as
we've said many times we are now in we
are now in an environment where crypto
will only produce a handful of winners.
People are becoming more selective about
what those winners are. Real utility
counts for a lot these days and you know
people are more easily able to sniff out
the the So I think yeah I
think good projects with with solid
fundamentals and good backing and a good
story can still do well but that's not
going to translate into everything
pumping like it used to. Ah you crush me
but you're right because uh a lot of
these altcoins they're going to have to
go away and I think it's a rotation of
capital but I could be wrong. So this
will lead me to Ben and I know this is
your favorite subject just like macro is
my favorite subject altcoins. So the
same question applies to you exactly. I
saw the face uh on that. And if we take
though a look at a little Bitcoin
dominance action, we can see that I mean
it was I mean 2021 70%.
And then of course and then we had the
great altcoin season of May 40%. Now we
topped out around June or so 2025
Bitcoin down at 65% which is great. And
now we're down to 58%. So, is this
sustainable or is this a counter trend
rally like you've seen before?
>> I mean, I think as always, I'm not
talking about your alt, right?
>> Um, uh, and anyone in the show not
talking about your alt. Uh, but if you
throw up my screen, this is, uh, this is
total three minus USDC minus USDT
divided by Bitcoin. And you know this
massive alt season that people are
talking about is literally just this
little move here, right? So I don't like
I just don't really buy it. I don't
think that all Bitcoin pairs are going
to have a longlasting durable rally
until after Bitcoin has a euphoric rally
itself. So until Bitcoin has a euphoric
rally, I would expect eventually the
collective altcoin market to just bleed
back to Bitcoin. Now recently the reason
why altcoins have outperformed Bitcoin
arguably is because the Fed funds rate
is not restrictive. Right? Yields have
gone up a lot and the Fed has not been
chasing the two-year yield like they
normally do.
>> Uh in fact the 2-year yield
>> if you approximate it as the neutral
rate, which is not really, but if you
just use it as an approximation, the
two-year yield is at is around 4.9%. The
Fed funds rate is 90 basis points below
that. Right? So, when you think about
when you think about like where the
two-year yield is and you think about
where the Fed funds rate was for
basically the entire last cycle, what
you'll notice, and let me let me put
these on the same scale. What you'll
notice is that the the um the Fed funds
rate
>> Mhm.
>> was basically above the 2-year yield
from, you know, from what, like 2022
>> until 2026, right? So, the reason right
now why I think you're seeing altcoins
have a rally, which again is fine, like
I mean I I I think you you people can
make investments whatever they want to,
but the reason from sort of a more
monetary policy perspective is because
the Fed funds rate is no longer
restrictive like it was for several
years. So then the bare case for alt
Bitcoin pairs eventually would just be,
you know, if the Fed continues to raise
rates, right, there's going to be a time
where likely the Fed funds rate gets
back above the two-year yield again and
then you would still likely see altcoins
bleed uh to to Bitcoin. So again, like
it's a long process. That doesn't mean
you can't make money in altcoins. A lot
of altcoins are doing well. Um, but
collectively, you know, they're still
not really durably outperforming
Bitcoin. Uh, if you look at if you look
at Bitcoin dominance,
uh, we actually have it on here where
you can you can look at it excluding
stable coins, you can see, I mean, still
at like 65%.
Um, I kind of think we're, you know,
we're kind of in this ballpark over here
in sort of the context of the last
cycle. And remember last cycle dominance
did not in the last business cycle
dominance did not top until after that
final parabolic rally that Bitcoin had
in like late 2020 early 2021. So even
though you could see altcoins outperform
Bitcoin in the short term uh I still
think eventually in order for in order
to have a a true drop in Bitcoin
dominance where it's going back down to
like 40% or something, Bitcoin would
have to have a euphoric rally first. So
that's kind of where I am on all Bitcoin
pairs. But that's where I've been on it
for the last six years.
>> And of course, and when I take a look at
the at your ex post, everybody likes to
remind you about all these different
things. So, yeah, this has been Ben has
been been very consistent on these
things. I gota tell you, it's worked out
pretty pretty decently. So, let's let's
get into the last rapid fire questions,
get in Q&A, and we'll get out of here.
Ben, I'm gonna direct these these last
ones to you. The most and rightly so,
most overrated narrative in crypto right
now. That's the first one. one chart
that you check that almost nobody else
does. And the last one is if you could
have one person to speak at the ITC
conference which is November 21st
uh 20th through 22nd, excuse me. Who
would that person individual be?
>> I I wouldn't mind having some I mean I
know this is kind of stupid. I wouldn't
mind having Jerome Powell come talk. I'd
like to get I'd like
>> Yes. Exactly. I'd like to hear I'd like
to hear what he has to say after because
the last time we heard him really talk
uh at an FOMC was he was he was saying
that the next move would likely not be a
rate hike and it you know and it like I
don't know if you guys remember that but
he would say that very very frequently
when people would ask him
>> and I'm like all right well like what do
you think's going on now and and you
know what are your thoughts because I
feel like he would provide a little bit
more forward guidance than Kevin Worsh
would. Uh, and so I' I'd be curious as
to what he has to say. So that would be
one to answer. Um, what were the other
questions?
>> The other one is the most overrated
narrative in crypto and then one chart
you check that nobody else does. Even
though you you do daily daily videos,
I'm sure there's one that you like. Oh,
this is a good one.
>> I mean, I think I look a lot at how the
long end's lining up with risk assets,
right? You know, and and kind of like
where those windows come from. I'm
trying to think of there's some other
charts that I'm looking at. Um, I mean,
I look a lot at like stable coin
dominance, but I imagine a lot of people
are looking at that, too. Uh, so maybe
that's not really one. Um,
>> no. Well, I mean, I don't stable coin
dominance. You can find that on your
site.
>> Yeah, I mean, I I look at stable coin
dominance a lot, like USDT dominance or
USDT dominance. You know what? I I'll
show you one that I've looked at um uh a
fair amount. It's uh let me I guess I
need to share my screen again. Um,
>> and then while you're pulling it up, I
you know what would be great about
Jerome Powell to be there is as he
speaks and we we listen to him but then
afterwards to ask him the real questions
like, "Hey, what do you really think
Kevin watch?" Oh, he's doing a horrible
job. That'd be good stuff.
>> So, this is a chart I've looked at a
lot. This is this is Bitcoin dominance
plus USDT dominance plus USDC dominance.
So, the reason why I've looked at this
was because, you know, I've sort of been
under the impression that we're just
going to be spending, you know, some
time at these highs like we did last
cycle. And you we kind of see we've
already done it a little bit, but I have
a feeling that we're going to spend more
time at those highs, especially
considering that the business cycle is
going on, right? In order in order to
have this drop, you would need a reason
for looser policy, right? like much
looser monetary policy, but you can't
have much looser monetary policy until
there's a reason for much looser
monetary policy. Um, so that's why I
kind of think this chart will continue
to hang around the highs for a while.
So, that's kind of what I've one of the
things I've been looking at. So, that
would answer uh and and actually another
thing you can do to to make it a little
more interesting for the altcoin people,
you can add in ETH dominance as well and
and kind of just see how how la how last
cycle you didn't have that alt season
until you actually broke through this
sort of barrier. Um, so I I think it's
an interesting chart because it just
shows you that in order in order to get
like this move down where which which
would be reflective of an alt season,
right? In order to get that move down,
you would almost argue that you first
need to break through here, convince
everyone that altcoins are truly dead
against Bitcoin and then it goes down.
It's just that that final move up, who
knows when that's going to be because
we've been at these we've been at sort
of these like range highs since June of
2023. So, nothing's really changed.
>> Nice. Okay, I got to use that. Guy, same
thing for you. Three different questions
there. So, what's the what's the what's
the what's the overhype narrative yet
again? what do you think about uh or
what would be the uh speaker that you
want to actually have
>> at ITC?
>> Uh overhyped narrative I think is
probably privacy. That might sound like
a controversial answer. I I only think
it's overhyped because I think 99.9% of
the population don't care about it one
single bit. I think I think it's really
important and I think it's you know
rightly there are people out there
shouting about it and underlining how
important it is but no one gives no one
gives a
>> about it you know it's just like and and
I think I think crypto people can shout
about that until they're blue in the
face but it won't make any difference
like people are just fundamentally
incapable of of I just don't think they
understand anyhow so yeah I could talk
for a long time about that so privacy I
think is an overrated narrative, not
because it's bad, but because people are
stupid. Um,
uh, speaker, I would go for maybe
Stanley Draen Miller because
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He to be tied to
everyone, you know, people in power, you
know, people in in in in high authority
like he seems to have mentored uh a
great many of, you know, a great many of
the decision makers out there at the
moment and has been there, done that,
and um also has, I think, some
interesting things to say about crypto
as well. So, he'd be my choice, although
I think Jerome Pal would be would be
great as well. I'd pay to watch both.
I would I would love to see like what
what Dre says, Gary Gendler there so he
could take like a victory lap on all of
us and and start dunking on everybody.
See, told you so. This is what you
wanted. This is what you got.
>> I mean, it was so obvious when he
resigned that the memecoin gate gates
were just going to flood open, you know.
>> Yeah, exactly. All right, everybody. So,
all great answers. I appreciate you guys
coming on the show every every week. And
then uh next week we are on guy's
channel, I believe. But if we got some
questions, we'll do a couple minutes,
then we got to get out of here. We're
kind of going over time. I apologize.
So, let's see. What do we got? Oh, it's
a good one. I think Benny, you did a a
video just recently about stocks. I
can't remember. What do you What do Ben
and guy think about Tesla? Good value
here, overvaluation. And then my next
question would be, do you think that
it's going to be SpaceX under the big
umbrella that is Tesla? Everyone wants
to take it? Go right ahead. I got I
picked up some Tesla at like 140 and
then again at at 220. Um, and I've I've
just been holding it since then. I I
missed it at 100. So, I ended up getting
it on like the higher the two higher
lows after that. And I've just been
holding it and I would I'm probably just
going to continue to hold it for now. I
mean, I I don't think the business I
mean there could be corrections for
sure. Like maybe there's a correction in
Q4. Uh but even but regardless of
whether there is one or not, I mean I I
think the business cycle will likely
live on uh especially through the you
know the the anthropic IPO and the open
AI IPO. The open open AI when is not
until next year. Um so I I would I would
still and I also own SpaceX too. I mean,
I did a video on SpaceX when it came out
and basically saying, look, normally a
lot of times, you know, they rally for
like a couple of days and they drop for
a few weeks
>> and then that ends up usually being kind
of like a a reasonable entry.
>> Yeah. Reasonable. Guy, same thing.
Tesla, do you do any of that stuff or
not really?
>> I don't own any Tesla. I mean, I own I
own Tesla through ETFs and things like
that that buy indexes, but I don't own
Tesla directly. I I think it's a very
interesting story at the moment because
what is Tesla going to be going forward?
I mean that might sound like a stupid
question because like duh it's a car
manufacturer but like I find it really
interesting that they haven't released
any new models for a very long time if
you forget the Cybertruck um and seem to
be really sort of pitching heavily into
robotics which I think is is potentially
huge you know could could maybe end up
being even bigger than cars but that's
the thing that kind of gives me pause
about it is that I don't really know
what what the what that company's
fundamental ally about anymore.
>> Yeah. Well, who knows? Who knows? But I
think there's some overvaluations, but
again, if you believe that the
debasement of the currencies happening,
why not get in there? Real quick
question. Hey Rob, is Tron a good buy
now? Not so for sure. It's been
sideways. It's an altcoin. It's one of
my best Bance, Ethereum, Salon, Tron.
And then uh what about this one? How
about this is this is another thing that
we get we get a lot. What's the best
price to enter Bitcoin for those on the
sidelines? For me, it's just it's
dynamic DCAN and I use the big three,
which is Ben's website. I have it on
Tech and Moneyline and Wes's SMC bot.
And I use the the risk levels and as the
risk levels go down, I buy a heck of a
lot more. When the risk levels go up,
buy a lot less. So, you guys got
anything?
>> I mean, I think I think DCA is the right
fit. I mean, normally you just buy
second half of the midterm year and then
you celebrate a couple years later.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's right. Guy, anything
with that one? Last one. We'll get out
of here.
>> No. Yeah, do the do do whatever. But I
think if you if you try and wait for a
best price, then you may you may end up
waiting too long. Do you know what I
mean? It's like if you want to hold some
Bitcoin, hold some Bitcoin.
>> Yeah, worked out pretty well, especially
as time goes on. Anyhow, well,
gentlemen, thank you so much everybody.
If you're not following these guys, what
are you doing with your life? There's a
link in the description. You can check
that out. But that is it for this one.
We'll see you guys next week on Guys
Channel. Thanks much everybody. Adios.